Tell me how you think I'm wrong, when I say I feel so lost, tell me why you think you're
love, erase all that it cost, tell me why you look at me like I'm just a piece of dust,
tell me how you think you know when I give away my trust.
Tell me how I'm
a little bit. I got a good show
for you. Oh,
provide the content.
Let's go.
I had a nice snap. I'm all
refreshed.
Oh, the most chaotic terror reading ever.
Let's see.
Thank you, Twipkick, for always getting the good stuff.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Twipkick.
I love you.
Twipkick, Twipkick, you're awesome.
You are awesome.
Twipkick.
How's everyone doing?
You ready for this
Come on boys just crap
It is funky. Hey, you got something to show you guys you want to see
How I'm treated
In this panel verse. What's up with the fuck eyes? Let's watch how I'm just the other I see how I'm treated in this panel verse
I'm gonna see oh
I got some stuff for you. I am. Oh, I've been better. I've been better, but you know, it's a new day. It's a new day
It's a new day
All the things that I used to say all the words it got in the way
All the things that I used to know have gone out the window
Ready let's watch
Hey Kaseaki, why don't you come up and show us your fucking beta pose with your little
American flag-thonged bitch.
Seers is cooking tonight.
The fucking weirdo?
Why don't you go lay in a fucking puddle a fucking goddamn kitty litter fucktard?
You haven't realized you fucking bitch the only reason why she's over there
It's because you have an audience sometimes and she wants to fuck beta over you didn't realize her contents beta it ain't you face boy
It's not you and your little fucking weird-ass pussy cat you got over there.
I have a question for you, psyche.
Are you that broke that you actually have to charge people to open a fucking panel?
I mean are you really that goddamn broke that you have to charge people to start fucking
No, he's just that he's just apathetically disparate. Did you guys see his new advertisements?
Come join my popular panel. I'll give you readings, but I don't even know what the fucking death card means
But I can show you my fucking tank dressed in American flag in my baby
It is a real sight
No, I watch
Watch fucking beep. I watch fucking Jenny
Watch fucking trip kick because I'm watching four hours of some gay guy pretending to be a psychic fucking beg for money for fucking
Fuck out of here
So fucking weird perverts all up in there all the time
Fucking weird
Let me tell you something if Jimbo was up there telling women that the only way they could get up on the fucking panels
If they show their tits, they would fucking roast him
About being a sexual
Fucking psyche can sit up there and say well you can
If you show your fucking shlong you you're a gross out motherfucker
He's laying on a fucking puddle of kitty litter, fucking talking about how he's the devil.
You're a fucking weirdo, bitch. The only reason why you get any attention that you do is because
you're a hell of a weapon. So, so Shannon, Shannon, can he come up here and give you a
tarot reading? I'll pay for it. Oh, please allow him. So I would love to fucking rip his little
American flag shit up his ass. You hear that sight? I say you five dollars for a tarot for
Yeah, I let's see how will you read tarot. Tell me what the death card's about again
Because you totally fucked that up
I don't know
You so you say he's been reading them wrong the whole time. Yes. He doesn't know what the fuck
Tarot in his name he
How's he trying to act like he's a celebrity and people want to see him when he's looking
with a bunch of old women, fucking cats, sleeping on fucking kitty litter,
and writing a fucking e-buck to get fish tacos. Are you guys really buying that shit?
She said it. You're killing him.
Give her a reason. She said you don't read the cards right.
Oh my god.
Prove to us that you read the cards right.
Yeah, right.
Hey guys, so am I gonna be treated fairly? Am I gonna be treated fairly?
Am I gonna be right? Is there any way I mean
Is there any way I'm gonna be treated fairly? I know they're not going in but just continue watching
That's a read is from you man
You giving me roll read is gonna tell you what they really fucking mean because he goes all over the place
Like he's full of shit. He doesn't know what the fuck any of them fucking mean. You know how long I've been watching tarot
Tell me again how the death card is uh, what was it? You said it was it was about
Something something someone in your life leaving you
You talking about Santa Santa you can't tell me because I'm telling you I got I pay for readings from him
So you telling me that he read to me the wrong shit
Tell you the one fucking time I saw meaning he said the death card was about leaving something behind or whatever
That's not what the death card is about. It's about new beginnings
It means the end of a fucking right cycle in your life. It has to be in
Right now
Just watch his little Disney princess cards
Talking some shit about the four of cups motherfucker doesn't know shit about cards at least get out the key
They give you in it fucked hard and read what they mean
$5 for the cats yet. I've never seen him buy shit for his cats ever I've seen him buy an e-bike
I've seen him fucking ride to the fucking beach and buy fish tacos. I've seen him try to get the butcher's fucking phone number
I've seen him fucking pull his legs up like he was a fucking female and his little fucking red white and blue panties
But I'm seen doing to ship by ship a lick fucking goddamn snatches of women that he think are more popular than him
Well, hey, where's your trilogy out there? Where's where's psyche's beauties not one of those fuckers talk to you anymore dumb shit?
And that's for a fucking goddamn friendship
I
Here's the truth
Fucking truth, you know what you were you were cannon fodder
Beedah brought you to be brought those fucking people to your fucking place because she didn't want you to fucking have a real stream
She didn't bring you to Sam man's
She didn't fucking bring them to fucking capes. She didn't bring them
She brought them to your channel and none of us knew that
Fuck you were you were just one of her weirdos that she fucking had in her back pocket
So instead of losing her channel, she could fuck with yours. Good job
Such entertainment
I'm looking true that you can have a good set.
I pulled the cunt card for her, so she got that.
That's her first card, OK?
Yeah, exactly.
That's about how much you owe your card.
All it is, that's her only card, too.
That's her only card.
You're looking very deep right away.
Aw, you called me.
And I didn't know how to read your text.
All right, I'll let you know.
And show your car as you read it,
so you can see that you can read it right.
Yeah, yeah, let's see the card card.
Yeah.
Let's see the card card.
I can't bet it's not appropriate for Kate's show.
I had to have more respect for Kate
than to get her a flat for her.
Show us the card card.
I want to see what card you take.
Just look between your legs,
and it's that smelly snatch between your legs.
That's all it is.
Well, you wouldn't know what a snatch looks like
since all you fucking smell is asshole.
Okay.
Wow.
You got me there.
You got me there, bitch.
Oh my God.
My cat's better than you, bitch.
Why don't you get out of Bootsy and I won't smell like shit you know like I don't even know you like
What are you talking about if you don't even know me? How can you talk? We you're talking about some character you see on
This is Shannon. She's a queen of the of Gen X
Never be the queen I am
No, don't worry. I don't want to be you. I didn't realize that turning your couch into a fucking litter box made you
Why don't you eat back a little bit?
I don't know how she knows me.
How does she know so much about me?
She sounds, she's like, I don't know zero about her.
Well, because you get to lift because you're an LOL cow.
You're an LOL cow, so they clap.
Really, well, milk me, bitch, milk me.
How about some fresh grass?
How about some green grass?
It's really hurt.
Honestly, because you're having a little bitch shit.
I don't know if I can see up there, kid.
Okay.
Go.
Go be sad.
Bye, psyche.
Bye.
I know.
Only member here.
You have to respect me a little bit.
Psyche.
I had a premonition, I was going to hear some dumb
plots screaming about me on a show and then I came over here
and I think I'm perfectly, I'm perfectly, oh gosh, make sure you
pull out the key for the card so you actually know what they mean.
I don't need to wait for the garbage.
I've been doing tears and I was eight years old.
Okay.
So by the way, and every year old, they're so gifted doing
It started, it's called like, you know, you learn over the years.
Well, I've been doing tarot since I was two.
So I win.
You haven't been doing tarot at all, have you?
Yes, I have.
I do tarot every fucking day.
Okay, well, you know you should be careful about disparaging fellow readers. The karma is really bad on that. Oh, yeah, okay
I'll worry about my karma as you're spreading. I don't even know you
Okay, give a show like how do you know? You have the public fucking stream that everybody clips because you're a total retard
I have a reading party. Give you a fucking shut up. I'll give you a good reading
But if you don't want to shut up
Little mad
Deuteree and Syke, Deuteree.
Mary made me, so, okay, so I will,
I'll do the reading, okay, so.
Okay, this for Shannon, this Shannon's reading.
Shannon, do you receive justice for something
in the recent past?
I don't know if that was a successful court case
or something in the recent past,
but you, something was made fair for you.
And you've also got, like,
oh, you see all these options available to you now
because of this, but it's a lot of confusion
because of it, because there's so many,
you're gonna wanna pick the one
that you most gravitate towards.
that looks like something to do with love because there's like a two of cups and this is like you
know two equals um meeting and you know starting something that can grow into something bigger
you're also coming up as queen of wands and so you've got a lot of good fiery power this is also
like the norman bates mom card okay whatever no he has it right also because you are like some
more about that card what's the more about the card well it says courage confidence independence
That's what it says. That is Norman Bates' mother.
If you ever stop psycho, that's Norman Bates' mother, okay?
That's Queen of fucking Wands.
Somebody go look up with a Queen of Wands representation.
It says, courage, confidence, independence, okay?
Yeah, that's what it says, okay?
Yes, so that's Norman Bates' mom.
Okay, lie some more, because it's not going for you.
Go ahead.
Okay, well, whatever, whatever.
I'm going to do this quick reading for you.
Okay, finally, we have the ten of...
the ten of wands which means you've been carrying some burdens you've been carrying other people's burdens
Maybe because you're in this queen energy like a lot of people go to you for help and things like that
No, you don't know but it is very heavy. It's like how do you got burdens going on in the future
Shannon is correct the queen of wands is passion confidence charisma and
fierce independence symbolizing someone who boldly pursue
Their dreams with courage and enthusiasm this card
Yeah, you're doing it since you were eight, but you can't even get the cards right.
I got all the cards.
You don't even know to look to see if the cards reversed, you fucking tarred.
I told them reverse, so they're not reversed, you fucking tarred, okay, anyway, they'd come
out reversed, they wouldn't just turn them upside down on my own, okay, well anyway,
you know nothing about tarot, so whatever, so, okay, thank you for having me on.
I guess that just leaves one score to settle.
He can't hit me.
Then let this be our final battle.
I love that guy. I love that guy. Okay, that was that. I have something else to play.
Let's see what else I got to play. What else do I have to play? What else is in my little
I gotta go to my history.
By the way, I wouldn't recommend doing a reading
under duress, but you know what?
It's, you know, Kate's panel, you know,
who knows what's gonna happen there, right?
But that was pretty rude.
Okay, anyway, let me have a look at my history.
I got something interesting.
Heat oh, I low-trip kick, but you see it was not funny. I was I thought I had to find you under the circumstances with that
Gorilla screaming at me. Okay. Anyway, what a cunt. Okay. Anyway
Fuck beta beta sucks
Then show up bitch
Come on
For you to sit there and call my friend a fucking rat. No fuck you beat a June be the jewels fuck you
You want the pants back? You want to continue blackmailing your ex friends that you screwed over?
I don't give a fuck anymore. I'm done
You literally are shitting on Jamie who's my fucking friend
Literally pitting people against each other which is uncool. You're literally fucking crazy
You don't give a shit about me beta when I was in Cali
Not once did you ever let me come to your apartment and we were so-called besties. I
Let you into my life with my mom
Fuck you beta. Hate you
And Rick if you want to continue talking to beta you can lose me, too
And you know, I'm gonna call like this fuck Ella and fuck controller fuck more fuck. I'm sick of the drama. Oh
How about I call this out beta
Maybe stop talking sexually on me because you're really embarrassing when I was getting my hair done
It was a really embarrassing call
And even from an outsider looking in she even thinks you're the common denominator
Pitting people against each other. So fuck you beta and damn straight
I did tell gamble we had a fallout you want to know why you threatened to call the police on me. That's why
Sick of this shit
Just wait
You suck it this bitch is nuts
Call the police on me, but you have my nudes weird, right?
Okay, go ahead do it call the cause I'm gonna fuck you go from calling the cubs to to literally saying happy birthday
Then you sit there and say oh I
Use you for money
You're gonna throw your gifts into my face from the years before
Because I got Jamie that ring that ashtray didn't want her to get
How about I give you your fucking pants back to that I never fucking wore cuz I knew you would do something like this beta
You want to know why you lost all your fucking friends beta because you can't fucking keep a secret that's why
So who's the rat not Jamie? You're the rat beta and you know what you want to know why I've been in so much shit
The past like let's see in the Abba shit. It was all because of you beta you beta
You live in some fantasy land and let me tell you you and your friend
You're in your 40s
acting all sexual
Make that make sense
Like I said, the oranges don't even exist.
And if you actually think, if you actually think
anyone can 5150 me, Bita, you're a fucking snake.
Because if I was at your place, no one would have 5150 me.
Because you know what? It's bullshit. That's a bullshit excuse. You know what's sad when you do watch this live
Hey, you wouldn't even invite me to your front porch. Yeah, Gamble at me
Don't care if I show up on his front porch some friend you are really beta some friend
Yeah, you fucking snake-ass bitch
You cause a lot of the problems on yourself beta because this is what you do
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum
I'm sick of you so beta go take my nudes and shove them up your fucking asshole
You lying as a bitch
You're the biggest snake and all you do is hurt people and then you wonder why I get pulled in drama
It's because you're the one that's messy as fuck not Jamie you beta
So guess what shut my middle finger put it up your ass because I'm done with you for life
Fuck you
You care more about stupid podcast with Michael Doyle's than your own friends. That's the damn truth
You don't even ask anyone how they're doing
You lost all your fucking friends because of you beta because you try to play
Sides and you know what the ones that are loyal are the ones that aren't snitches
So go take your ass back to Ella and try to manipulate again because it's not gonna work
because you tried to use people as weapons.
You're using Karen as a weapon,
you use me as a weapon, you use other people as a weapon.
But you never admit when you're wrong, Bita.
And you let me take the fall every fucking time.
And I'm done.
You sit there, you talk to Karen and you know it.
So don't put that on me.
Fuck you beta go shove my bacon now up your fucking ass and go crack an egg in it because I bet it'll stink
Jamie and Nancy have been nothing but really good friends to me and they care about me on my birthday
You know what you you know who didn't give a fuck about me on my birthday beta
Beta your gas lighting your high manipulation wasn't gonna work this time and they have worked when Aaron died, but I know better now
And now I'm more aware and you know what? I'm really going to call you how it's like, okay?
Imagine being in your late 40s and having your friends boobs shown on a podcast
Real classy, right beta class classy beta, right?
Come on. Give me a break and
You want me you want me to expose some more? I think you're the one who really dogs Abba because you're the closest to her
Look at how many people you burned over beta
Look how many people you fucking backstabbed look at how many screenshots you have
Where did I get all that shit from you?
All the way back in 2020 because you were sharing gambles discord stuff to
Me and Abba knowing it would trigger us. So you're messy as fuck beta
And you know what a real friend doesn't show just because my nudes went flying out
No friend goes to my like you beta you literally said you sent me my own news and said what would your parents think of these or
Well, how would you feel if your dad sees this? So you have to be the one that sent it
So maybe I was right on that part
Like I I like Jamie Jamie's a great friend Nancy great Karen. Hmm. You know
She can be good, but be to stop using people as weapons stop going behind people's backs
Maybe for once think about other people and not just yourself
Because you do buy your friendships and you try to get them to do what you want to do and you try to make everybody be your bitches
That's not gonna work here
And to be honest
beta
Fuck you and your tramadol.
You wouldn't know why?
Because that shit isn't a psychiatric meds.
That's a painkiller.
So when you're done doing drugs, then maybe come back.
Hold on a second, I've never seen any of this.
Never seen any of this.
I
Don't I don't I don't know
Mmm. Oh my back
This is insane
Yeah, I don't know
Hmm
Anyway
Mm-hmm
Okay, what's up guys
Yeah, so I've been told
That's all beta we'll have fun with your real friends
Katie
Sweet pea and
And thank you for treating me like less than garbage.
Well, since it's over, I'll just go ahead and...
Please don't contact me anymore. I refuse to take abuse or be your punching bag.
You have blamed me for everything and forgiven everyone else who makes fun of you, like I
don't get enough people lying on me.
I only stated facts and never ever mentioned you in a disgusting manner.
I was nice and cordial when I took your link, explaining the BS things you are mentioning
about Aaron's death.
I don't think it's funny.
I never laughed at you being sent stuff, not once.
I defended you and said the same thing happened to me, but I am a woman who lives alone.
J-dog has threatened me over and over I have sent you screenshots shots and you enjoy him making you feel like you are correct
I don't like liars nor people that take zero responsibility. You hurt me over and over. I
was nowhere
This panel where people made fun of you and giggled yet. You always blame me. Please stay away from me
I know who I am and one thing I am not is a liar
Okay
Oh please low-key please yes the real Jesus too
Yeah, well
See yeah, it's Jesus christ
I don't know she's about to
What a mess
I want I want those clips of I want to find clips of me
Saying terrible things about her
Terrible things. I want to find clips of me disparaging her business
But me trying to put her friend, you know friends against each other. I
Mean I want to see that
Can someone produce those I
Don't think so
As you know why
When it's over
That's the time I fall in love again
And when you go go go go I know
Casey your ass ain't getting up here until you pay that fine
That is finale you are the male
Katie is a
as a j-dog says and so
not gonna listen to your burpin Mike or
Your non-tent
Unless
You can sponsor, you can sponsor the panel.
What?
Oh mercy me, what?
I never heard this before.
You're the only person, you're the only person I have that role for.
Because of what you said to Elisa.
Hi, Jesus, and Jesus, you were blocked in the chat.
Okay, guys, a lot of people were blocked.
I had to unblock like 60 people.
I think this was Alexander.
Yeah, Pam Sugar Tits.
I'm not, I don't have to put up with it, but by the way,
I do have like new open panel rules too.
Hold on.
Because, you know, I call me a,
people want to call me a locale, okay?
Like I said, give me some grass, green grass, some milk, me bitch.
Here's the new rules.
Not very difficult.
Okay.
You can't mod? Well, even Alex, I had to take away Alex's log, right?
But that was them. You can also see them on my community wall.
Not even, I mean, I need my, like from now on, I'm just like, there's no, like, modding isn't, you can't read the code of conduct is full of spelling mistakes, let me have a look, let me have a look, it's a spelling mistakes one, let me see.
H-A-R-A-S-S-M-E-N-T-S-L-A-N-D-E-R-J-O-R-N-I-N-G-P-S-Y-C-H-E-A-W-A-K-E-N-S-C-O-N-D-U-C-T-A-C-C-U-S-A-T-I-O-N-S-D-O-X-X-I-N-G-Z-E-R-O-T-O-L-E-R-E-N-C-E-A-N-G-P-S-Y-C-H-A-W-A-K-E-N-S-C-O-N-D-U-C-T-A-C-C-U-S-A-T-I-O-N-S-D-O-X-X
I'm standing
Just like yeah, I mean there's two what what which is the other one?
Yeah
Oh someone made it yeah, well, I think she had that planned anyway. Hey, Jamie. Hey, Jamie. Hey, Jamie. Yeah, I
Think she had a planned but I'm sure
Like what I didn't I didn't even watch that video
Yeah, well somebody can you know what yeah 25 and
You know if someone wants to sponsor KZ step right up step right up and you can sponsor him
Two weeks probation if he's good then he gets smart I mean
I'll give him panel access
I
Just figured you want to know the new revelations j-dog made on Jimmy's panel
There's new revelations. What can I just go watch Jimmy's panel? I
Mean what j-dog saying like he's you'd have to be very sneaky to go
after today and then go
I'm too smart for you
Sounds like you think you
Pretty much but revelations you're gonna share some great revelations with me. No
It's like I've been saying for about probably a month, you know, it hasn't changed and it's like
Like I said, you guys don't case you went to a Lisa's discord, which I got him back into he was banned
And I asked the Lisa if she would let him back in that was mistake number
I mean, I've been some stupid past mistakes. I am just fucking dumb and
Then he goes in there and says oh
Lisa don't you know he's talking all this shit about you and he's saying you're the worst shriever
He's a better shriever than he was I never fucking ever said right
Guys anybody see that panel I can ask Janet about I'm sure she watches
It's just a joke. That was a joke
That was a joke that was what was it nobody laughed nobody laughed
She didn't believe it because it's not true and she knows me
You know with you
Find the clip it guys find the clip find one clip where I even said one negative thing about her
You're gonna go try to ruin my relationship. You're gonna do that. Why were you mad? Why are you mad? Oh?
because
the panel thing right I
And again, let me just
I'm not gonna read like you know this woman this woman ham sandwich woman
Well, I'll tell you her text again. Not not this is ham sandwich. We need to know who that is. You see ham sandwich woman
I was ham sandwiched my birthday. Okay, let's see
Did she say tell the fucking truth
You came for me and one in my place. What place?
What place that I want Miss Hampton language Jamie's words not mine remember the fire
No
You came at my deceased niece
What?
Do I know?
What okay, who does that seriously? She kelp. I love you, too, Jamie
Jamie did way too much shit like, and I'm not going to repeat these allegations,
to never let him agree the laws of my niece to her cronies, blah, blah, blah, blah,
to harassing the baby daddy, I couldn't fucking breathe.
She smothers, I didn't have a life from her drama.
Okay.
She was, oh God, okay.
One is okay question hurt. Okay. My birthday wasn't about you, but you sure as hell tried to make it about you
The narcissistic versus you pole you made it sound like it's my fault. I also never talk shit on beta
Follower, are you kidding me?
That's you all day every day.
Hold yourself accountable, stop lying, sweet pee, bronze, etc.
Are attacking back, stupid?
You started this.
You dox me, motherfucker.
No one knew my name till you kept saying it first and last.
I have that recorded.
I don't know her last name, okay?
did maybe get confused and say her first name because I knew her about her first
name basis and then she came under some like you know very long name and I just
you know remember I just had her first name made that a docs to the first name
saying the first name I don't think so I don't think so
You dox me, motherfucker, okay?
Um, proof states otherwise.
I did say you probably have bed bugs.
Probably.
It ain't just your bed, dumbass, it's your entire house.
You're an idiot.
You want to fight?
Let's go legal, shithead.
Try it, bitch.
I'm done playing.
Keep your name out your mouth.
I hate you and you're a worthless POS.
Poor cats deserve so much better.
In fact, do us all a huge favor and go away.
With pleasure and Chameleon bans you, and bans you.
Oh, flumsy, it's been pretty good.
So please.
Be that have fun. What great what great friends you have now sweet pea
Bronzebird and Katie and you know, whoever else, you know
Have fun. I'm just sure I was just some monster, right? I was a monster, wasn't I?
Wasn't I a monster to you?
What did I do?
My mom, what did I do?
Yeah, that was.
Well, J-Dog does a better one, I think.
J-Dog is better.
It's a ham sandwich.
Yeah, Jamie, I know.
Somebody said Arby's, can someone?
Yeah.
This is as bad. This is as nasty as they'll get about it, you know, and I'm hurt
And she and then she has the nerve to oh, she's hurt and
What was it about why she hurt?
Again, well J-Dog said this. I sent you screenshots of what J
Oh
Sweet piece the homie
So, if you can go shove a biscuit up or twat, okay?
And, uh...
Let me know.
Taste the biscuit!
I do too.
I do too. Here, I'll be right back. Hold on a second.
Shut up
Oh, I'm sorry, I'll be right back
and stripes flash flash turning into tacos with the cider with lash fish guts on the
mic got salsa in my eye i'm dancing on the table like conspiracies don't die
Wow, it's really rich, right?
Isn't that really rich?
Isn't it rich?
Oh.
I mean, dear God.
Oh, blaming the victim.
She's sitting literally with the guy that's doing it to me.
Literally sitting on a panel with the guy
doing the shifts in me.
Like literally, literally,
lapping at me.
Maybe not about that specific thing,
but
Sitting up there lapping at me
Smelly I love you, Jamie and I'm so Jamie
Hey J-Daw come on Nancy my friend
Jamie if you want to come up and talk
That wasn't
Okay, well, but I was polite. It's kind of my father passed away from cancer. It's not any kind of things
Hey, Barry Barry, how is that clip though? What do you think very?
Considering the circumstances, I thought I did pretty well with that that monster with that monster Shannon on your panel
Oh, I'm not yeah, and I thank you for um, yeah
Yes, it's yeah, it's not
It's not fun, especially like I was saying like person that
he was um
Someone said something about oh, yeah, it's mostly about cancer and I was just like that. Oh, yeah
This guy hell walker. So this guy hell walker I knew he ended up taking me to the this King Diamond concert
You know how beat it would always say oh
You know clumsy and Emma hates you and you know you just treated them badly
Here's why clumb this woman clumsy clairvoyant not clumsy in the chat. This woman clumsy clairvoyance. Well, I introduced her to
I always I donated this woman. I was in her chat. I was very so
This guy hell walker appear in the scene. I met him at Emma's. Okay, and then oh, he's has stage three or four terminal cancer, right oh
The you know just the man of sympathy and oh, yeah, you know, just you know, oh my gosh
Oh, I'm you know, I'm peeing blood. I mean just like yeah, all just going into very graphic detail about his cancer symptoms
so
I posted a picture of him that when he was here, with tricks on his lap, right, and then
I posted nearby.
Hold on.
Your election rally between beer. Yeah, then yeah, and I posted maybe like, you know, nearby. Hey, I have a new boyfriend
I think I want to talk about me sir. Maybe they're talking about some guy on grinders. I don't I don't remember exactly
But I wasn't talking about him
So he was just like he blocked me in you know traveling gypsies chat
He told all of them to like oh, I'm some kind of monster, right? Okay
Okay, she's a real person
Yeah, and no modding with feelings, please. No money with that's what Alex was doing
Then I had to unmod him and now he's timed up for the day. I didn't do it somebody else did
Yeah
Yeah, like I said this guy lied about this guy hell walker, okay
So he was so he told clumsy like you know and other people too
This woman to galactic miss this like a lot of people there's a bunch of people that I it was in this group
Just drop psyche like don't talk to him again. It's like you know, he's most evil person
You know, he's he's hitting on some straight, you know, I'm a former, you know, it's Royal Marine Afghanistan, whatever and
Oh
Clumsy drop me. Oh, I went to her chat. Get the fuck out of here psyche. Get the fuck out of here
Turns out he would baking cancer. He didn't have cancer, but then they started dating
Okay, and so that's why club this woman clumsy clairvoyance never forgave me
Because then she started dating him and then she would then she'd like later would say to me
Well, it was no I wasn't mad about him
Really yeah, it was sick it was sick and then he like
Karma, sorry, he dumped her ass for the other chick galacticness. He was her mod and shit
But she never she never gave me
He never forgave me, okay
Other people realize what happened and you know, I was able to make up with some other people
But I never treated anybody bad. I never said
How are you Barry?
Yeah, I never gosh
Yeah, maybe I did make occasional jokes like you know gay jokes and stuff like that
Like maybe like one time I said a gay joke in the chat like and I like when I was really drunk and I was like
I said basically oh hell walker
You know stayed over but we didn't touch or something or like, you know
I said on my side of the couch. He said on his that's basically all I said. Whoa, you would think I said like, you know, I was
Licking his butt or something. I don't know. It was just like hey careless Kate. What's happening?
Well, you were there Kate. What's happening?
You have to rewind a little bit
Yeah
What's happening wars happening? Well, I know, you know, it's fine. I mean
Was it gonna be war? Like what did I do? I'm like see I was declared on me war is declared on me
Like who's tough now? Oh
Berry horn
Who's tough?
Like who's tough? I
Can't
We're saying it's tough. Uh, is that the real Jim Nick?
Yeah, but I'm talking about this other this woman named clumsy. That's a terror leader that you know, okay?
Hey, mister
It's okay. I'm sorry
Is that the real Jim Nick, okay, yes Jim Nick, what's up girl?
And I don't want to I don't want to like get in the middle of this, but I'd like, you know, I don't want to like know
All I'll say is
You've been always really cool to me. I've never had a problem, and I
Don't know I just like I have a problem with how you've been treated by a lot of people
I think I think I've expressed that to you and I hope you're okay, okay?
Bluebeam that's how I'm KZ talks
KZ talks like that. And do I know you? I've never seen this person bluebeam before. That's how KZ talks
But Casey's gonna come up like some voice
Casey I'm not like dumb, you know, I know energy, okay, I even if that's not how you would fit
I just know the energy about it
Okay
Do I know I don't know why does someone in blue beam?
Ask for the link that I've never seen
Right, it just doesn't make sense
Does that make sense guys said some brand of like today some random person I've never met before or heard of
He's gonna show up and then he wants the link to come talk on my panel right now
Who are you? Do you have something relevant to add? I mean, I don't understand. I'm sorry
It's like I don't think I'm wrong about this. I just feel the energy
Because despite what people say I am a psychic, okay?
And I did like the flip kick clip flip kick clip. I liked it
Time
Time you're losing points as a mod
Second by second. Okay time
No
No, I'm not some kind of like
You know chuch up the up the you know the wagon of the up the turn up truck or whatever. Okay?
He could say
I'd like a reading or something, but no, he's saying that he's talking like KZ asking for the link
When I'm in the middle of this right. Oh, yeah, gosh, okay. I don't know
Hey, come on. Hey, Jim. Okay, Barry. I hope you have a relationship where you're able to the joke like that
I really come on. Don't pick on Jim Nick, please
Yeah, homie Johnson, I'm no yeah, I'm no choose off the turnip truck. I really am not
No random person's just gonna come out of the blue
blue beam and
When I come on panel in the middle of this and say
Hi, I'm new here. Can I get a reading?
Well, you know, it's
Now I already said that was my mistake. Okay, I don't remember you warning me about that specifically, but
You know my mistake
My mistake I made a bud. I've had a bunch of mistake. I'll take responsibility from some for some bad decisions
Homie Johnson, you're just I mean I can't tell this energy. I know the energy. Why is she so desperate to get on panel Casey?
I told you you can come up
You pay the fine, right?
Okay.
Please, please, please don't tell me how to feel.
Please.
My Grouch, oh my god, here they're back.
Hey, yeah, J-Dog, no money with feelings, because I already had enough with Alex.
I mean, Alex was high, I mean, there were 60 people hidden.
I had to untime out 60 people.
What's BS, uh, hold on.
Oh yeah, J-Dog, okay.
Don't maw with your feelings, please.
I don't know, is there, is he?
J-Dog, come on.
So Jay Dogger, what are you doing?
Well, let me see, let me just look at the messages
you see, believe it, if it's feelings, let me see.
Mike Roche.
Why are you going back in for like,
the guy's name is Mike Roche.
It's like, you know, that he's that important to be here.
I mean, really, is Mike Roche really the,
that an integral part of this chat?
Smelly is my crotch. Okay
Who's this torn this night person?
Torn snake
Your smelly. Oh, hey, why are you banning smelly? Oh
My gosh guys guys guys guys guys guys I need to like
Do like some serious like
Yeah, no modding with your feelings, okay?
Well j-dog
It's okay. I mean, it's like well, it's like I know I'm saying I agree with like, you know
Don't don't make fun of j-dogs. No, but really it's like
Not that big of a deal
Jada you're a very good-looking guy, but I can't I can't so you can't go at home. What are you talking about?
Anyone want to come up on panel though? Yeah here. I'll have you up on panel. Come on anyone. Kate want to come up. Jamie
clumsy
Jada, I mean Jada, you know, you did have a good run this this morning. I mean, is anybody else want to come on panel?
What's going on?
Barry you want to come up? Let's have a chat. Let's have a chat chat. Okay
Jim Nick want to come up
Okay, here we go
Yo psyche what's up, bro? Hello, how are you?
Good good, bro. Dude. I'm blocking the one same person's account. It's that smelly
They keep saying all you have a cancer is growth on your nose
They got that from black RG and now they're rolling with it. I hid that one Barry keeps on hiding it
I blocked it. They came back on another account and they're asking me the same thing
That's what I did
Block them like I'm like personal block and then it's like they say
Threatening stuff or like I mean, it's like it's kind of just like light for all. I mean, it's like we know you don't have
No, I know. No, it's just annoying. That's the only thing and then they got buried
Like from you
Because it's like then everyone's just up in arms about it. It's a big distraction. Okay, I'll go ahead and get that psyche
So that way, you know, there's no there's no excuse. I appreciate it. No problem. No problem. Are you okay, bro?
Well, what's going on man? You're okay?
Well, I because I didn't catch it bro. I was I was at work bro. So actually I didn't catch it like what happened
She wrote you like a personal message
Well, I wrote her and I said well
You know have fun with your real friends, you know, Katie sweet pea and
Um, Bronzeberg, and then she wrote back, and I said, oh, I said, thanks for treating me
like worse than garbage.
And then she said, tell the fucking truth, oh, no, that's another person, hold on.
Then she said, uh, yeah, hold on one second, okay, hold on, she said, okay, so, then she
Please don't contact me anymore. I refuse to take abuse or be your punching bag
You're playing me for everything and forgiven everyone else who makes fun of you like I don't get enough people lying on me
I only stated facts and never ever mentioned you in a disgusting manner
I was nice and cordial when I took your link explaining the BS things you were mentioning about Aaron's death
I don't think it's funny. I never laughed at you being sent stuff
Not once. I defended you and said same things happen to me, but I'm a woman who lives alone.
J-Doc has threatened me over and over. I have sent you the screenshots and you enjoy him
making you feel like you are correct. I don't like liars nor people that take your responsibility.
You hurt me over and over." And then she posted the link from the Twipkick thing. She says,
Near this panel where people made fun of you and giggled yet. You always blame me. Please stay away from me
I know who I am and one thing I am not is a liar
Dude what the hell
Max
Well, you know, it's not over right you know that that she's gonna come back
As far as like this is she's just saying that right now like
This isn't over. This isn't over. You guys are both good. You guys are get past this man
You guys are gonna be I have a feeling I have a strong feeling you guys are gonna really reconcile this
And I want you guys to reconcile it see it
Because it's like she's decided shit for months since like May and I've been taking like talk about taking abuse
I mean, it's like slandering my business like the whole reason
Okay, let's, you know, let's, hold on, I'm going to mod the real gymnast, because there's
so many fake gymnasts.
I'm just going to mod the real gymnast, okay, so I know the real gymnast, okay, but no modding
with feelings or no, okay.
No attacking anybody keep an eye on the jet already Alex. I had like I was insane to mod Alex Alexander
Did you give him energy mod?
What's up?
Get getting Alex to get Manigee mod Alexander McQueen managing mod. He got regular mod and then he
What the hell he went to town on everybody, huh?
Don't know I don't mind. I don't know. I'm hide Jesus Christ. I don't
Ziggy and there's like a bunch of people and a bunch of people I have no idea who they are and stuff like that, right?
Yeah
But yeah, good, I have a fair
What do you think this age like what else will never learn?
This stage by the way, thank you for like at least like saying I was welcome in kks chat this morning
You know I went kks at this morning to say hi and then it's a kid out of here
It's like you're not welcome here not her but it was people in the chat
I was like, I'm not welcome here and then this stage was like you're fine. You can be here or something like I don't
I don't know why people say it's like right
but uh
You fuck-ups wouldn't even chat if you didn't have that little wrench to age you it's
You're a tenitude troll, but you're actually okay. I don't know what's going on. I mean it's like I have to
Watch people okay
So
Here's here's the problem that I have people saying I'm gaslighting how my gaslighting if I'm
Pushing for both of you guys can reconcile this gaslighting
Is it healthy is it healthy for I don't know it's like I mean it's like I
Feel like I've just been like
You know, they just like treated like worse than garbage
Uh, Mason.
Jay Dogg.
What's up, Mason?
Hey, Jay Jay dog. Were you trying to fit me earlier because love like our G was saying stuff that I couldn't believe like he was saying earlier
Yeah, yeah, I was backing you up black RG. He's a liar man. Don't believe him. He's a troll
He tries to slander me. He'll talk shit about you. He's don't don't believe him. Don't listen to him
That's what that's what he does that's what he does he's a piece of shit just ignore him
He's he's he's he's he's he's
he's he's he's he's he's he's
All he does is try to fuck with people online and I stalk and harass people. That's all he does all day 24-7
Jay dog the thing is he I think I agree with the other state because he started something that I never even heard of because he said like
Oh, don't believe what Jay dog says. Why I mean, I never said anything like about that. You know, yeah
I know that's what he does. He's trying to slander my name. That's what he does
That's why it's like I just ignore him like he's crazy
Jay dog just ignore him like right
Yeah, yeah, just block them. That's what I'm gonna do just block them from here on out because that's what psyche says to do
You know, I don't want to you know
Just click on the person's name and then go block and then I won't even have like usually the chat on the screen and so you
Won't yeah, because the thing is J dog. He has nothing to do with me anyway, so I never talked to him really
Yeah, I know he just came at you for no reason. That's what he did. That's what he does. Jay dog
That's exactly right. Yeah, he came at me for no reason
Yeah, he attacked you that's what he does. He likes to attack people especially when they're like not even knowing what the hell's
Going on and has nothing to do with them
Yeah, I can agree with you Jay dog. Yeah
the carvers was discord gang stalkers and beat out was one of their main goons
like i said gang stalking that's the feeling i get right right i was just watching gang
stalking too and it just gave me like ptsd about it people were like oh it's not gang stalking
Well, they have a bunch of people coming after one person like a common enemy like a like a gang literally like what it sounds like a gang is like
stalking a certain individual
Like what they harass and they go after a person
And they're constantly fucking
They start a silent news left to me
Yeah, that's what they do man. That's what these trolls do
Yeah, I mean gangstalking is real and I've had experience with it. Okay, so it's not a joke. It's like it's scary. It's
What else is it when I have like
Every day the past week I've had people at six in the morning come banging on my door looking for scrap metal and I had it right
It's like what is that?
You love the intro Sam and are you just being specious can you keep saying that but I don't even play it
I played a different intro. I don't know
I don't know. Why do you keep saying that but it feels like it's like not
It might be a fake man. What's the real Sam in? Oh, is it okay? Oh, he said it's a clone him in chat
Okay, but it's the exact same
Everything and you're talking right. I don't know
Okay, Mike butchers been are you better smell it all like it's smelly the to clone you in the channel
Okay
Yeah, it's him
I know it's him.
He's lying so I mod him.
Psyche, what do you mean it's him?
It's like Sam-Man?
I'm talking to Sam-Man.
He's trying to get a mod for some reason.
I don't know.
I'm really going to just be unmodding people.
Modding people right now because it's like I have the mods just go in wild like it's like you know actually today
I had people saying oh, we're sending people to your house not one mod. I mean there's a lot of mods in the chat
Nobody did anything and I had to do it and it's like
Well mod if they're saying they're sending people to my house
They're saying they're sending the cops to my house and stuff like that just hide them and then time you work
You kept unhiding them you just time it up for a day when I was hiding when I was hiding them
Yeah, I see times is double agent. He can't be you can't he
Pee-pee's the homie if you were say I'm friends with sweet pee I'm fine with that
We say sweet peas the homie that implies like
She's cool with all bunch of people right? I don't know in my mind
That's why they're cool like more than just like that. Yeah, like the home
I know that you and I work cool and stuff like that so I can understand that man. Yeah. Yeah, we're cool Mason. We got no beef
Yeah
Yeah, there's no I mean fix him like why would there be a big same and same and salmon what?
You're a big help Sam and it's like we I could have had a nice discussion with be the last night over 10 minutes
You kept interrupting first of all in the first 10 minutes, and then I said well tell me before like the 10 minutes is up
No, you didn't you waited until you know
Got that got that dollar, right?
Whatever. Okay. Hold on. Who's this this?
She's just Jim Nick hold on one second
just make sure we get the real thing in here to me hi how are you hi okay so
you're you're trying to say basically that your mods like you're like like
hiding them meaning like infinite infinite
and they're like then changing it to a timeout, right?
Well, that's what time did.
Like I was, I kept hiding like people that were saying,
we're sending people to your house
or the police are on their way, you know, and stuff like that.
I call the cops on you and then I would hide them
and then he would like, he tied them up for 86,000 seconds.
It was like a 24 hours or whatever.
And I was like, time stop and then he did it again.
But I, and then he, I don't know, I like time
Bad things about me though. He was in that chat the other night, you know, where's one's like fucking shitting on me, but I
Just like I just need to trust my mods and stuff like that and it's like and
Really if someone's saying they're they're threatening like you know me or anybody else in the chat
You can just hide them, you know
That's the thing kind of that's that that's the thing right there psych some of these mods like
They're we're not all aligned up like some of these mobs. We don't get along with each other
Yeah, oh
24 hours. Oh, I want to see them tomorrow. You know, they'll they'll they'll come. Yeah, that's what they do. So they'll under don't undermine
Okay, don't undermine what the other mod does. That's what they do, man
Wait, I'm the channel. I'm like
It's like they got supposed to like
Maybe we're doing at the same time or something like that, but it happened a couple times
going on that
but
Yeah, dude
So did they actually show up after that happened they said it in chat?
Well, that was like right at the end kind of like at the end of the earlier chat today like
Someone named uncomfortably numb then said oh the SWAT teams come into your house
And then it's like and beta quickly called somebody and said that's not the real Katie like
But why would somebody be pretending to be her like I don't understand. It's like she's not she's like kind of like irrelevant
Don't know. I mean that's what they do on discord. They like play these mind games with you to fuck you up
And then they'll use and they'll use that live. This is what they do site. Trust me
They go on discord. They'll use you as their locale, right?
They'll play a bunch of fucking mind games on you salmon see Chanel because he has his own fucking discord
He does the same stupid shit there. So does Barry
and they'll fucking sit there and they'll roast everybody like I went on Barry's fucking discord
and like the entire thing was just like roasting me the whole time and Barry's like oh I know well
I believe it's a superb tune because of that yeah
I was like why the fuck would I want to be on a discord where everyone's just dogging me the whole and you see
And I see the messages come on member key had that special like or she had a thing about me
She's like oh psyche the weirdo lurker because I was seeing the messages where they're talking shit about me and allies talking shit
About me pop up and stuff
And I think while I was doing the show and I was acting and so I was like what's this is bullshit
I'm just here to like see these messages and shit. I'm not crying Barry. I'm just saying that your discord is pathetic
Did you guys content if that's your content of your fucking discord?
It's just like roasting a nobody someone you haven't even fucking met in real person
You fucking have more problems than fucking we ever do okay bitch
And I don't do the good Katie impression, that's J-Dog that does the good Katie impression.
You do the ham sandwich, J-Dog.
Oh, what are you talking about?
Oh, I'm Katie.
I'll have a ham sandwich from my birthday.
That's how she talks. That's how Katie talks.
She talks like that, like a KZ, like a female KZ.
Hamster
From the other night by the way from it was on quick kick
Can I play that is it okay if I play that I mean it's like everyone see that it's like kind of short
It's just like a yeah, it's on trip. Thank you. No, she shouldn't get mad. Nobody should get mad about that because it's on a trip
Kid it's not on
Okay, so here we go. This is this is the other night on
It's panel. This is really funny trip quick. It's on quick to kick by the way. This is a
You guys can see how I'm treated. Well, not the key. I'm not saying Kate or Barry
I mean, there's this woman on the show this woman Shannon or something. Oh my god. This is monster. Okay, just check this out
Take this up
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
Heirs
Why don't you come up and show us your fucking beta pose with your little American flag song bitch
Seas is cooking tonight the fucking weirdo
Why don't you go lay in a fucking puddle of fucking god damn kitty litter fucktard?
Yeah, they realize you fucking bitch the only reason why she's over there
It's because you have an audience sometimes and she wants to fuck beta over you didn't realize her contents beta it ain't you face boy
It's not you and your little fucking weird ass pussy cat you got over there.
I have a question for you, Psyche.
Are you that broke that you actually have to charge people to open a fucking panel?
I mean, are you really that goddamn broke that you have to charge people to start fucking talking?
No, he's just that he's just epithetically disparate. Did you guys see his new advertisements?
Come join my popular panel. I'll give you readings, but I don't even know what the fucking death card means
But I can show you my fucking tank dressed in American flag in my baby
And then we tell you, so you do watch sight, you do watch sight.
No, I watch the fucking clip.
You watch, I watch fucking beep.
I watch fucking Jenny.
I watch fucking trip kick because I'm watching four hours of some gay guy
pretending to be a psychic fucking beg for money for fucking fish.
Get the fuck out of here.
I forgot what that I'm on.
So fucking weird curve, it's all up in there all the time.
Fucking weird
Let me tell you something if Jimbo was up there telling women that the only way they could get up on the fucking panels
If they show their tits, they would fucking roast him
About being a sexual
Psychic is sit up there and say well you can oh
If you show your fucking shlong you you're a gross out motherfucker
He's laying on a fucking puddle of kitty litter, fucking talking about how he's the devil.
You're a fucking weirdo, bitch. The only reason why you get any attention that you do is because
you're a hell of a wimp. So, so, Shannon, Shannon, can he come up here and give you a
tarot reading? I'll pay for it. Oh, please, allow him to. I would love to fucking rip his little
American flag shit up his ass. You hear that sight? I say you five dollars for a tarot for
Yeah, I let's see how will you read tarot tell me what the death card's about again
Because you totally fucked that up
I don't know
You so you say he's been reading them wrong the whole time. Yes, he doesn't know what the fuck. He's doing
He might as well get up some
baseballs parts and pull out Joe DiMaggio and say
How the fuck you got tarot in his name and he can he read the car
How's he trying to act like he's a celebrity and people want to see him when he's living with a bunch of old women,
fucking cats, sleeping on fucking kitty litter, and writing a fucking e-buck to get fish tacos.
Are you guys really buying that shit?
She said it. You're killing him.
They were reading. She said you don't read the cards right.
Oh my god.
Prove to us that you read the cards right.
Yeah, right.
Because that's fucked.
Hey, that's because I got Sarita's from you man. Hey, did you give it me roll re is gonna tell you what they really fucking mean?
Cuz he goes all over the place like he's full of shit. He doesn't know what the fuck any of them fucking mean
You know how long I've been watching tarot. Tell me again how the death card is
What was it? You said it was it was about
Something something someone in your life leaving you
Are you talking about Santa Santa you can't tell me because I'm telling you I got I pay for readings from him
So you telling me that he read to me the wrong shit
The one fucking time I saw meaning he said the death card was about leaving something behind or whatever else
That's not with the death cards about it's about new beginnings
It means the end of a fucking right cycle in your life in a beginning one
So I can tell you right now
Then he pulls out his little Disney princess cards,
talking some shit about the four of cups.
Motherfucker doesn't know shit about cards.
At least get out the key they give you
and it fucked hard and read what they mean.
Well, they need $5 for the cats,
yet I've never seen them buy shit for his cats ever.
I've seen them buy an e-bike.
I've seen them fucking ride to the fucking beach
and buy fish tacos.
I've seen them try to get the butcher's fucking phone number.
I've seen him fucking pull his legs up like he was a fucking female in his little fucking red, white, and blue panties.
But I've seen him do shit by shit by lick fucking goddamn snatches of women that he think are more popular than him.
Hey, where's your trilogy out there? Where's, where's Psyche's beauties? Not one of those fuckers talk to you anymore, dumb shit.
And that's her a fucking goddamn friendship.
Here's the truth, Psyche. I'm gonna give you a fucking truth. You know what? You were you were cannon fodder
Beedah brought you to be brought those fucking people to your fucking place because she didn't want you to fucking have a real stream
She didn't bring you to Sam Man's
She didn't fucking bring them to fucking capes. She didn't bring them
She brought them to your channel and none of us knew the fuck you were
You were just one of her weirdos that she fucking had in her back pocket. So instead of losing her chain
channel, she could fuck with yours. Good job. Such entertainment.
Who the fuck is this? Who is this? First of all, Shannon.
You'll never find me.
You have a channel, you're just a more relevant bitch.
I'm the fucking truth.
What is this? What is this?
First of all, I pulled the cunt card for her, so she got that.
That's her first card, okay?
Yeah, exactly.
That's her only card, too.
That's her only card.
You're looking very deep, right away.
Aw, you called me.
I didn't know how to read, Terry.
I know.
I showed your car as a reader, so we can see what you can read or write.
Yeah, yeah, let's see the card card.
Yeah.
Let's see the card card.
I can't, but it's not appropriate for Kate's show.
I had to have more respect for Kate than to get her up.
Show us the card card.
I want to see what card you take.
Just look between your legs, and it's that smelly snatch between your legs.
That's all of this.
Well, you wouldn't know what a snatch would look like since all you fucking smell is asshole.
Okay.
Wow.
You got me there.
You got me there, bitch.
I think that left shit.
Oh, my God.
My cast is better than you, bitch.
Why don't you stay out of Bootsy?
And I won't smell like shit.
I don't even know you.
Like, what are you talking about?
If you don't even know me, how can you talk?
You're talking about some character you see on.
This is, this is, this is Shannon.
She's a queen of the, of Gen X.
She ain't queen of fish.
She's queen of the sea.
She's queen of the fish.
I'm certainly not the queen you are bitch boy that's for sure never be the queen I am
Yeah, don't worry. I don't want to be you. I didn't realize that turning your couch into a fucking litter box made you
In my video
Why don't you eat back a little bit
I don't know how she knows me.
How does she know so much about me?
She sounds, she's like, I don't, I know zero about her.
Well, because you get the lift because you're an LOL cow.
You're an LOL cow, so they clap at me.
Really, well milk me bitch, milk me.
How about some fresh grass?
How about some green grass?
It really hurt.
Honestly, because you're having a little bitch shit.
I don't know if I can see up there, Kate.
Okay, go.
Go be sad.
Oh, boy, thank you.
I know.
You're a fucking holy member here.
You have to respect me a little bit.
Sigh, Kate.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
I had a premonition. I was going to hear some dumb
plot screaming about me on the show. And then I came over here and
here you are.
Perfectly.
Oh, gosh.
By the way, make sure you pull out the key for the card so you
actually know what they mean.
I don't need to wait for the garbage. I've been doing tears
and I was eight years old. Okay. So by the way,
they're so gifted doing terrible.
It started, it's called like, you know, you learn over the years.
Well, I've been doing tarot since I was two, so I win.
You haven't been doing tarot at all.
Have you?
Yes, I have.
I do tarot every fucking day.
Okay, well, you know you should be careful about disparaging fellow readers the karma's really bad on that
Oh, yeah, okay. I'll worry about my karma as you're spreading your news in america
Okay, give a show like how do you know you have the public fucking stream that everybody clips because you're a total retard
I have a reading part
I'll give you a good reading, but if you don't want to shut up
Little mad
Do the reading, Syke, do the reading.
Mary gave me, so, okay, so I will do the reading.
Okay, this was Shannon, this Shannon's reading.
Shannon, do you receive justice for something
in the recent past?
I don't know if that was a successful court case
or something in the recent past,
but something was made fair for you.
And you've also got, you see all these options available
to you now because of this, but it's a lot of confusion
because of it, because there's so many,
you're gonna wanna pick the one
that you most gravitate towards.
That looks like something to do with love because there's like a two of cups and this is like, you know, two equals
Meeting and you know starting something that can grow into something bigger
You're also coming up as queen of wands. And so you've got a lot of good fiery power. This is also like the norman baits
mom card, okay, whatever
Also, because you are
Some more about that card
What's the more about the card? Well, it says courage, confidence, independence. It says norman baits is mom
that's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That's what it says. That
There yes, so that's that's not a date. Okay, I like some more because it's not going for you. Go ahead. Okay. Well, whatever
Whatever, I'm gonna do this quick reading for you. Okay. Finally, we have the 10 of the 10 of wands
Which means you've been carrying some burdens. You've been carrying other people's burdens
Maybe because you're in the screen energy like a lot of people go to you for help and things like that. No, you don't
But it is very heavy. It's like how do you got burdens going on in the future?
Shannon is correct. The queen of wands is passion, confidence, charisma and
fierce independence symbolizing someone who boldly pursue
their dreams with courage and enthusiasm this card encourages you to
authentic self and brace creative endeavors
Okay
Yeah
But you can't even get the cards right
You don't even know to look to see if the cards reversed you fucking tarred
Reverse so they're not reverse you fucking card. Okay. Anyway, that would be they come out reverse
They wouldn't just turn them upside down on my own. Okay. Well, anyway, you know nothing about tarot. So whatever so, okay
Thank you, Kate for having me on
I guess that just leaves one score to settle.
You can't hit me.
Then let this be our final battle.
that was a good one. How would you think Jim next? Are you there Jimmy? Jim? Hey, sorry.
That's a pretty good fucking appearance. I in my opinion. I like that, right? What am I doing? I'm
Do you like Shannon or just like her? Oh, yeah, she's a joy. She's a wonderful wonderful woman. Actually, I just love her
But it would have
Right ray of sunshine in my day, but you know what?
There was like really no way it's like whatever. It's like I got everything
Perfectly right and then take it fuck that was
Norman Bates' mother on the card, by the way.
I mean, it takes you.
Oh, what do you mean?
We're in Bates' mother's-
All right, clumsy, of course she would.
She was just waiting for me to get out of the hospital.
So she had constant fucking talk.
Hey, Summer.
That's the way she was.
We're going a little bit to know how it's just-
Her life is so fucking lame.
She has nothing else to talk about.
Yeah, that woman, Shannon, basically just irrelevant.
I've never heard of her, and I do not want to...
Come across her again. She was just I'm very unpleasant, but you know hey, thank you go out of Lupe. Thank you so much
Oh, thank you so much
Nice, and this is this is a person Alex was trying to hide today. Thank you go out of Lupe. Thank you
Thank you
I don't know, I don't know.
And it's just because people like Bita continue
to slander my readings and things like that.
And so, you know, she's calling me low cow and, you know.
Well, she has a way about her.
Look, I talked to her on the phone privately.
Thank you so much.
She does have a way about her that can come off a bit harsh.
I don't think she has malintent.
Shanna?
She was talking about the death card. It normally does mean like
like
Right means transformation. It can mean it can be can mean a literal death and it's like as for someone leaving you
Yeah, it could mean someone. Yeah, or like a new beginning like processing it, right?
Right, maybe so so and then she I don't know. She's I mean, I know what the cards mean
I know what the death card means. It doesn't just mean death, right? And I did I mean, I did yeah, so I mean
I know, like I said, I've been reading since I was eight years old.
It's like, and then you have this guy, yes, really.
And this guy-
How did you get into that?
Were your parents into it or?
My parents weren't, they're just not religious.
And so they basically let me explore,
like I wanted to explore.
I had, I think I had a reading, I had like a, you know,
like a,
bear or carnival or something like that.
And I was, I got really into it after that.
My sister used to ice skate and stuff.
And so there was a bookstore
and that was like one of the first things I remember buying
was like the mythic tarot and the tarot of the cat people.
And that's when I was eight years old.
And so...
I was also about the satanic Bible when I was like, you know
And everyone's like oh you're buying this and say like that I was always into the occult
I was always into it and so
Hey, hey, baby. Look at my baby. Hold on. Oh
Look at this cutie pie. Oh
How many cats do you have for?
Oh, I love it's eyes with the black and I don't know then I also have this who's this
other woman from the carter verse I mean did you you know this what do you know anything
about the carter verse yeah it's kind of where I stemmed from a little bit but I didn't
the Carter verse and she just I just came across this clip today and I just found
it pretty interesting because it kind of is I'm sorry guys it's I did play a
little bit earlier I just want to play just a little bit of it because this is
interesting because I don't know maybe you'll maybe you'll see something like
you know that is like you know a relevant or something let's have a look
Watch this look at this beat up. Oh
That's crystal Anne. She's kind of like you guys suck crazy
There you went up fucking play these fucking games and show up bitch
Come on
For you to sit there and call my friend a fucking rat. No fuck you beat a June be the jewels fuck you
You want in the pants bag, you want to continue blackmailing your ex-friends that you screwed over?
I don't give a fuck anymore, I'm done!
You literally are shitting on Jamie. Who's my fucking friend?
Literally pitting people against each other which is uncool. You're literally fucking crazy
You don't give a shit about me beta when I was in Cali
Not once did you ever let me come to your apartment and we're so-called besties. I
Let you into my life with my mom
Fuck you beta. Hate you
And Rick, if you want to continue talking to Bita, you can lose me too.
Uh, okay, so can I put some context?
I know I'm gonna be like this, fuck Ella!
Yeah, go ahead.
Okay, I don't really know that much about Kristen Ryan.
I think she said with Trisha, maybe? Did she? I think so.
But, um, she like pretended to have a baby or something, and it was like some doll.
Does anybody remember that?
I don't I didn't follow that long, but I remember I went on her channel one time because and Carter blocked me
Almost Instagram, and then he was running her channel on Instagram. He was like block. Hey, I was like fuck you bitch
Well, just got me I'll play a few minutes of it. It's kind of like okay, okay
This girl is on like social security. I believe she's like actually has like mental
I don't mean to say that in like a rude way like but she literally thought that this like baby doll was like her baby or something
Was there people like harassing Aaron Carter?
Yeah, but he was like psycho and like on drugs and you know he kind of invited it himself
Okay
Well, I'll just play a couple moments.
He would stream like 24 hours a day.
Yeah, I do remember, like he was, you know,
like came on Dr. Phil and he was like all strung out
on Dr. Phil and then it's like, you know,
of course he met a bad ending, but it's like, you know,
if he's on drugs and stuff like that,
I mean, is there such thing as like,
People enabling or people put I don't know is it like because kind of people are a product of their environment
Oh, yeah, definitely and especially like an X
kind of like super star celebrity. Of course, people like view those people as like some
special class, not as just like a human. And I mean, it's hard to do with people that are on
substances to like, know when you're enabling, know when you just want them to get better.
There are definitely a lot of people that were enabling them.
Uh, I wasn't talking about myself, but okay.
No, but you're projecting everything on to others,
but you're not looking into the mirror.
Um, I look into the mirror every day,
but thank you for your input.
How about you speak about yourself before you bring up others' problems?
Um, because we were talking about Erin Carter, okay?
That was the subject at hand.
We're talking about Crystal Ann, how she relates to that.
We're going to talk about you now, about that.
Hold on. Arthur.
Let's let's play the fifth. I don't want to talk about myself. I want to talk about it
Let's watch this is my thing that like we're talking about someone who passed away, right?
We can judge them all we want, but we can't judge this one Jim Nick
Thank you like oh my god, I have cancer everyone give me ten dollars a day like remember that
Give me ten dollars a day. I've never asked that once in my fucking life
Jim Nick doesn't it hurt your tongue to lie so much on the internet?
Does it not hurt your tongue to be so fucking judgmental without any proposition of any awareness of what is reality?
versus rumors and
activity
Judge of the mess
Okay, I'll get you can
Okay, well, let's give you a watch for one minute. I'm sorry. I don't want to like hey
Guess what Arthur's?
Sweep your fucking tongue side to side like a fucking snake like you fucking are
About you fucking use some tooth flaw. So wait, you don't have any teeth my bad. Oh
Yeah, I have teeth. I've played enough teeth to fucking bite your fucking
Off of your fucking neck artery off. Okay. I'm not okay. So you know what?
Really like if we're talking about air like the Aaron Carter thing right now
I'm just trying to get to the bottom of it. Like I don't want to attack Jim. Nick, you know, I
I know she has maybe going through some medical problems and I'm sensitive to people with
you know cancer and stuff and my father died of cancer.
But she faked it, that's the issue.
I'm sorry, what?
You faked it.
I faked what?
I just got a biopsy, it hasn't come back yet.
So then why were you telling everyone you already have it if you don't even know?
Because I'm I go by the wind of my blue jean shorts in the window the white shirt and my hair
I say what I feel in the moment
You see that you see that you see that's like she feels like oh, I got I feel like I have it
So I'm gonna say if you think that's okay
That's what the doctors told me at the time. So I posted about it. Should I maybe refract from it?
Yeah, medical stuff is like
Arthur Arthur Arthur
Arthur if you ever went through a fucking thing I went through guess what I would wish you hope and well
Not fucking sit here on your goddamn fucking desktop or your fucking iPhone or fucking whatever fucking stupid Obama phone
You have and fucking bash people over the fucking head, okay?
Look, don't get me wrong, I definitely do wish the best for you, alright?
No, you don't. Shut the fuck up. You're fucking losing.
Arthur, I don't want to... I don't know enough about it, and I don't want people being accused of that.
Well, why are we talking about the dead, then?
We're watching this, and, okay, but thank you, Arthur. Thank you, Arthur.
Alright, I'll stay here. I'll stay here.
Oh! But I'm sick of the drama!
Maybe stop talking sexually on me because you're really embarrassing when I was getting my hair done
It was a really embarrassing call
And even from an outsider looking in she even thinks you're the common denominator
Pitting people against each other. So fuck you beta and damn straight. I did tell gamble
We had a fallout you want to know why you threatened to call the police on me. That's why
Sick of this shit
I'm not the best for you just wait
Just don't like when you lie, that's all
Shut up the gym
Yes, okay
This bitch is nuts
Csimnek iznudsz.
the police on me but you have my news weird right okay go ahead do it call the
cause I'm gonna fuck you go from calling the cubs to to literally saying happy
birthday then you sit there and say oh I use you for money you're gonna throw
your gifts into my face from the years before
Because I got Jamie that ring that ashtray didn't want her to get
How about I give you your fucking pants back to that I never fucking wore cuz I knew you would do something like this beta
whoa
You want to know why you lost all your fucking friends beta because you can't fucking keep a secret that's why oh
So who's the rat not Jamie? You're the rat beta and you know what you want to know why I've been in so much shit
The past like let's see in the Abba shit. It was all because of you beta you beta
Psych is this that Pocahontas chick?
And let me tell you
She was like, yeah, I saw this clip of the RV, whatever.
Is this the girl that works at the Gulf?
She's like from Canada?
No, she's from like the United States somewhere.
Yeah, Paige, is this Paige?
No, that's not Paige.
Oh, OK, I'm up there.
But it's not Paige.
Is this Crystal?
So much better if it was Paige.
Crystal and from the car reverse.
Makes sense.
like I said the oranges don't even exist and if you actually think if you actually think
anyone can 5150 me beta you're a fucking snake because if I was at your place no one would have 5150 me
Because you know what? It's bullshit. That's a bullshit excuse. You know what's sad when you do watch this live
Hey, you wouldn't even invite me to your front porch. Yeah, damn
We'll let me don't care if I show up on his front porch some friend. You are really beta some friend
Yeah, I mean
Okay, on behalf of beta, I would never let these people in my own house
Okay
You just seem like a little I mean it's like people can come to their own conclusions. I mean it's like but yeah
She seems like you know, you know, there's something about crystals
I did that it's only about Mary's and that crystals, you know crystals if you name your daughter crystal just watch out, you know
Oh my god
You cause a lot of the problems on yourself, Eda because this is what you do
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum
Go take my nudes and shove them up your fucking asshole.
What?
You lying ass bitch.
What the fuck?
You're the biggest snake.
And all you do is hurt people.
And then you wonder why I get pulled in drama
is because you're the one that's messy as fuck, not Jamie.
You, Bita.
So guess what?
Shove my middle finger, put it up your ass,
because I'm done with you for life.
Damn fuck you
You care more about stupid podcast with Michael Doyle's in your own friends. That's the damn truth
They don't even ask anyone how they're doing
What are your thoughts on that site you lost all your fucking friends because if you beat us because you try to
Play sides and you know what the ones that are loyal are the ones that aren't snitches
So go take your ass back to Ella and try to manipulate again because it's not gonna work.
Because you tried to use people as weapons.
You're using Karen as a weapon, you use me as a weapon, you use other people as a weapon.
But you never admit when you're wrong beta, and you
And I'm done you sit there you talk to Karen and you know it so don't put that on me
Fuck you beta go shove my bacon now up your fucking ass and go crack an egg in it because I bet it'll sink
What?
Jamie and Nancy have been nothing but really good friends to me.
And they care about me on my birthday.
You know what? You didn't give a fuck about me on my birthday.
Bita.
Bita, you're gaslighting.
Your high manipulation wasn't going to work this time.
It's not even her birthday.
And they have worked when Aaron died.
But I know better now.
And now I'm more aware and you know what? I'm really gonna call you how it's like, okay?
Imagine being in your late 40s and having your friends boobs shown on a podcast
Bro classy right beat a class classy beta, right?
I think you're the one who really dogs Abba because you're the closest to her. Oh
Look at how many people you burned over beta
That's true
Look how many people you fucking
Backstabbed look at how many screenshots you have
Where did I get all that shit from you?
All the way back in 2020 because you were sharing gambles discord stuff to
Me and Abba knowing it would trigger us. So you're messy as fuck beta
And you know what a real friend doesn't show just because my nudes went flying out. No friend goes to my like you
Beta you literally said you sent me my own nudes and said what would your parents think of these why or what?
How would you feel if your dad sees this so you have to be the one that sent it so maybe Ella's right on that part
Like I I like Jamie Jamie's a great friend Nancy great Karen
You know so so you can be good, but be to stop using people as weapons stop going behind people's backs
Maybe for once think about other people and not just yourself
Because you do buy your friendships and you try to get them to do what you want to do and you try to make everybody be your bitches
That's not gonna work here
Can I just say something? Yeah, to be honest, I just want to give a different opinion real quick
Bita has never really sent me money. She sent me, I think, like, 11 bucks for some lunch for food on my birthday.
She's never bought my friendship. But, like, behind the scenes, she's always been so very caring.
It gives me, like, really great advice. And to me, she's a really good friend. I know that y'all have your differences.
I, I, I, yes, yes, we've had our differences, but we talk like mature adults and we work
it out.
Okay.
And that's what mature people do.
I've talked to her like a mature adult, like several times, and she continued to slander
me.
And continues.
Yeah.
And continues to.
Personally, okay. Can you understand where she's coming from? Can you understand where psyche's coming from?
I can't understand both their perspectives. I never like I never went after her anything personal like like about like, you know
Her her job like, you know like her thing and she's always like oh psyche just cares about
You know, she's another one of those fish tacos and dick. It's like a lot of these things
Yeah, a lot of these things that are said it's like she's
Well, the loud she has her whole legs to sweep peak that woman Katie like I breathed the text message Katie sent me
They say oh, you know, I like I started or something again sweepy and Katie and in Bronzeberg. I had no I
Don't know anything about them. I know it's like I don't know
Okay, this is the way I can I say how I see it
Something cuz you're Jim. Well, I can speak so Jim Nick
the first thing that came out of your mouth was well you know beat is a good friend she gave me
$11 for my birthday so literally the first thing that came to your mind is monetary no it wasn't
it wasn't i was going to the ladies like you're not listening because i was going to understand
So when Crystal was saying that she buys her friendships, I said, well, for me, it wasn't like I wasn't been like that.
Okay. Okay. So I'm
Setting my opinion. Okay. Well, I see what's happening between
psych and beta
beta put in a lot of energy and time to help psych kind of like
create a channel and like create like, you know viewers and then
And then to see him befriending someone who's attacking her personal family.
Right that goes a step beyond just
Butting up with Allied Baster computer who's currently sending scrap metal people to my house
All right currently sending Pete the unpaid pizza to my house who's currently sending manure to my house who's currently
striking you know trying to privacy striking me all the time and stuff like that and so
So, when is this in? When is this in?
Everything else is in.
It always goes back to uncle effort.
It always goes back to uncle effort, that kind of thing.
And it's like, I didn't say that.
I kicked Arthur off the panel that day.
And she's like, well, you didn't defend me,
so I'll never defend you.
I mean, it's like, okay, but it's like,
if every time I go into her chat,
it's like some kind of like attack on me.
It got it's a low blow. Yeah, like really and it's like really attacking my she's like, oh, you're stupid business
Like who cares you're losing like a dollar. I don't know. She's like, you know, that she literally said like I mean
It's like you can see these clips on strip kick then whatever you can see how I'm treated on her panel where she had that four people against one
It has to like I mean I was actually one it will do one-on-one with her last night on my show a little bit and
on Santa for 10 minutes before I was, you know, clapped off or whatever after, you know, exactly,
I got 10 minutes immunity and then right at the 10 minutes, I was like, okay, five, four, I just,
you know, so, you know, I didn't really get a chance to discuss, you know, discuss things with
her. I've tried and it's like, she said she's like, you know, not to call her, so I didn't call her,
now she's, you know, and then now she said not to contact her again because, you know, I said, well,
have fun with your friends, you know, Katie,
Bronzebird, and Sweet Pea, and thanks for treating me
like less than garbage.
And then she said, no, never contact me again.
I'm a liar because J-Dog threatened her or something.
I don't know.
It's like, it's always about somebody else.
It's always about this person said that
and I'm associating with them.
But she has people on her panel every day.
Just screaming about me. I'm disgusting. I'm covered in fleas and ticks and there's shit all over my floor and you know, it's like, you know
Yeah, she has you know said okay, she thinks I don't shouldn't think I have HIV
She does and she like did say to the HIV awakens tarot to like, you know change your name or whatever and she did
You know say she thinks I love my cats, which is like if anybody knows me
It's pretty obvious and it's like my cats are happy while taking care of but it's like, you know
There's a lot of these other
Narrations that are going on that she's happy to talk about and she was happy to go on
Bronzeberg show and sit on that panel and talk shit about me
You know and you know even there and there's other people that were on the panel too
And they just didn't like you know really go in on me and stuff there was hanging out basically
But she was just happy to like oh, here's my problems. You know, here's my here's what I think about you know all these
Very gets very it's got very very personal and it's like and I didn't get that personal
And maybe I'm getting a little bit personal today with you know some of this
But she's you know, she's basically told me to go fuck off and like you know, I and so
You know, it's like it's sad and it's like yes, she
Did bring a lot of people to my chat, but that's who had who had a good point that Shannon had a good point
She just wanted to what that's what Shannon's opinion was that she brought a lot of she went into like you know
Get some heat off of her and just like you know bring these people to my panel and so I don't know
I just I see the point in that she brought a lot of
Negatit like there's been a lot of negative. It's my fault because I did say you know, yeah, but I mean did I necessarily
I don't know.
It's like, yes, sometimes I was into the drama,
but I was always trying to work things out.
We always got along fine one-on-one on the phone,
but it's like, then it's like,
and I get along with her fine on her panel one-on-one.
And then it's like, she brings other people on.
She says, I accuse her of, you know,
I'm accusing her of these conspiracies and stuff.
I just quoted what she said.
She said, oh, they asked about her ex-husband,
They'll never figure it out in a really like, you know way that it's like what is she trying to like she's like trying to like see scary
And plus I don't like how she was like, you know said this thing about Alexandra was like she's like, oh, yeah clumsy was gonna
Go beat up Alexandra or you know something like that. I mean, I mean you can see these clips
Right, I mean, it's like, you know
so
And then it's like, you know, she's just she's she's been mean she's been and people have said wow
I don't like how she treats you and it's like she's bullying you and I'm like just so willing to
Overlooking and try to try it. I try to try it since May. I think it was like May
Like I was fine with her up in like from December or like last year up into like May when that thing with Arthur
happened and then ever since then it's just been like back and forth and I thought like be like look what's big degree and then
She started attacking me herself and it's like and then it's like oh she didn't say it or she was drunk or something
I got I've gotten drunk and said stupid things and stuff like that, but it's like
Oh
It got a really really
Nasty got nasty and it's like I didn't try I didn't get as nasty with her as she continually
Tried with me, especially it was slandering my tarot and then trying to turn
Me against people and telling people will it's him or me and stuff like that
And she chose these people sitting up on our panel and plus she wouldn't let me talk to her one-on-one
She was on her panel
She would always have to have all these people screaming over me for against one vibe against one and they're all yelling at me enough
She said
Even Kate, Kate doesn't like me very much, but Kate's like, wow, if I had someone yelling at me screaming my ear like that and then bronze bronze hop of that, plus my microphone was low, right?
She's like, I would have been upset too.
So, I mean, people can just come to their own conclusion.
Of course, she's going to have like, you know, a lot of people support her.
She has a much bigger show than me.
She's saying a lot of stuff that you just, if you're a friend, you shouldn't have.
be like trying to put out there and like things that are very untrue and it's like I can't
even really defend myself because I can defend myself on my show but it's like I'm not able
to
When all this is being said and it's like oh look at what's that his friend if she's saying it it must be true
And it's like and so system nasty self of them said it's upset me
Maybe we have gone back and forth pit for attack a little bit and it's like I think responsibility
I have not been a perfect person, but I have not gone
Like most of the stuff I've done has been a response to what is she mad about I did AI thought and then my AI is terrible
I'm not talented. I'm just like this like
terribly lame
Horrible monster person that I mean, it's just like just she's just
Painting me like that and it's like that whatever that woman was saying. I just related a little bit to that
But you know what, here's where I draw the line, is when it gets too emotionally kind
of like activated that there are people showing up now at your house, at her house, like
Well, that was like she had to kind of like set she has the guy on
Ally and he she was sitting on the panel cacawing with him
Maybe it wasn't over like you know the stuff being sent to my house
But she was laughing and with them about other points and stuff like that
They're all sitting on the panel like the other day on bronze birds two
He had two panels in a row two and a half hours thing. Oh psych. He's just I mean, it's just like I nine and then she's like
Accusing me. She's like, oh, I was like, oh play this thing. She's like, oh, so you can strike me
I would never strike. I would like I don't strike. I would never strike anybody. It's like and I
Gymnac, you know, I'm a reasonable person. Okay. I'm a reasonable person. I also don't like
How she
Treat you and some of the things I've seen. Okay. I felt that was bullying, but that's that's your relationship
I'm not gonna get in the middle that I just personally
And I'm sorry, you know an Arthur. I didn't agree with Arthur coming at you like that either and I don't know
What's that you I didn't I didn't like it you think I did like it you think I wanted him too
But I wanted you to be able to respond because I I don't know and I don't and he was saying the thing
But no, I've talked to you on Instagram and
Private like when we were when you were maybe like on an off time with her and whatever and it's like, you know
You know, I did express sympathy. I mean, I have several times
Had your back I have if you don't know I have and I've said, you know, I've told people don't pick on jenice
She's she has a serious illness and it's not right to be picking on her like that
And so if Arthur went too far
With that I didn't know if he was gonna start saying that and it was kind of just caught me off guard
But you know, I wanted to give you, you know, I mean of course and he said you you can of course respond to whatever you want
To say about him. I'm not trying to bully you. I'm genetic
I'm not trying to get you on my side or whatever
I understand if your friends with her and I don't have a problem. You can go it, you know do what you want
You know, I want you to be happy. I want you to be healthy
I want you to like live your life and you know, it's like if you know hate me or whatever. It's okay
Um, I don't, I don't have a problem with you. I've never had an issue with you.
Why would I have anything against you? I know, but it's like she tends to like,
want to like have people choose sides. Like, and I don't, anybody.
be friends. No, no, no, we both know we've talked about this before. We know that we're both adults
and we can deal with our own issues ourselves and not to take sides and that's like a mature thing to
do. It said it's him or me or like if you go over there you can't come over and she's like tell
that and then and it's also like it's like all these people that were here like all of a sudden
it's like they're over there saying horrible things and these are her mods and it's like you
But it's like her mods talk magic if I go over there 90% of the everybody's against me including all the mods
So she comes over here
Maybe a 10% or somebody and it's like and I don't necessarily know her history with some people so sometimes she has the
Relationship where they can go back and forth and stuff. I don't I don't really try to get in the middle of other people
I would always always always like be that
Keep it between like whatever like our relationship. Why does all these other people always keep getting dragged into it? Because people were trying to
Definitely cause problems between us because they thought they think it's funny or whatever
And it's like but she lets them win and she does
I mean she just let them win and it's like am I happy? No, is she happy? No
It's like but they're all happy and it's like that's what I said to her and I gave her
I wrote a nice message the other night and then I found out you know
he was like saying some other really bad stuff and I got really upset
based on something because she's bringing other people I know into it and she's always been saying
oh well look at you did to Emma and clumsy and it's like she doesn't know anything about their
personal relationship with them but she's like so just like acting like I was
at fault for all this stuff.
And I just found out today the guy was taking cancer
that was like, you know,
I think there's a guy at Hell Locker
that was taking cancer.
And that was the reason for the clumsy clairvoyance
that whatever it's like.
So, I don't know.
It's like, I just like, I guess.
I guess I I don't know I feel bad now like no, I mean I think it's good to vent to someone that
it's kind of like, you know friendly with her and I
Yeah, and you're you know, I like you
I've always I've always like like you know, it's like I remember I went on your show and like these are big pipes
And we like did the belly dance
And it was just fun. It was just fun.
Oh, yeah.
And I'm sorry about getting back and stuff.
I love good times like that.
We have family.
I mean, like good times.
I meant like, like having a good time like that.
I didn't, okay.
I didn't feel like I love good times.
I know a good time is going to watch him be like,
she loves me.
Big Pipes is like a band again for my show
because he said the n-word like 20 times in a row,
like try to give me.
Oh, no, maybe it's not.
That's a Vanguard.
Are you okay?
Vanguard, what's up with you?
How long, Psych? Are you aware of that?
I've heard you've had a lot of disturbance in the force recently.
Disturbance in the what?
The force.
the force
The force okay like the force like the start Star Wars kind of force or what a lot of disturbance in the force
Hey, wait wait wait psych psych. I'm gonna go
Carded by a new car for herself
Um but thank you. Thank you for
talking to me. Okay. But I do
hope things get better. Okay?
Okay. Thank you. I appreciate
you. That's what happens. You
know, I respect you and I wish
you the best and I hope you're
happy. Okay. Thank you. I
appreciate it too. Okay. I love
you too. Bye. Before you go,
it's a gym or gym night. It's
gym and it's like you can call
her. You know, it's a gym night
So how are you doing sake?
Well, you know, I've been better, but I think I'm on the right track, you know
I'm kind of like standing up for myself finally
Don't I feel like I let myself be bullied and it's like well, I can't like you know, it's like oh, I should you know
I don't I'm not gonna go. Yeah, I don't I'm not trying to say. Oh, you know treat
You know, I do like, you know, I do respect all women and it's like I'm not trying to like attack a woman and stuff like that
The beta and I it's like she really has really
Gone and hard for me. The reds are coming. I'm so nice. So I page so now that it's gone on
Back and forth like this and maybe there should be a middle ground
Consensus and a way to move forward because no one's getting anywhere this way
I agree prairie, but it's like I guess the only way is for me to you know
I'll just like this will be like the last you know, I'm just gonna
I just kind of have to
It sounds like it sounds like you've concentrated this
Malficiency in all of your stream tonight
Malficiency we mean
Well, it seems like it's still talking about stuff that happened yesterday
No, this happened today. This has happened today. That's got that. I got the message today
I don't know if you've been watching
Apologies, but anyway, do you know what?
Do you know what duck feathers are you remain?
Dog dog
Freemasons or what?
No, do you know what water of a duck's back meat?
Okay. Yeah, I know water of a duck's back is but it's like when you're being slandered and people are believing the slander because it's turning into an echo chamber and
It's just like constant and then it's like I'm being
every morning
Scrap metal workers coming here and knocking on the door and it's like
I mean she's on the panel with them and it's like she's fine with them and they've docked her and they've sent stuff to her house, too
And it's like she's she seems to be fine with all these people
But it's always me that is supposed to be there. So I know I'm not I'm not gonna try to attack her
Okay, I said I played in a fight with
That you showed today about the door dash people and you said
Yolandi, Yolandi, Yolandi, is it paid for? No, go fuck yourselves. I didn't see that today.
I didn't say go fuck yourself. I said, oh, it's a prank. I'm not I'm never rude to the people like
And that is my front door on a right without necessarily fix the issue
I don't know if that would fix the issue putting a thing on the door because people are still I mean adults will come
It's still people coming in the property. They have to come all the way back on the property
My front door is on this guy's channel as old channels and clips from my show and stuff like that
He has other personal thing of other people on there, too
That is basically doxing people's relatives and stuff.
I don't know it's like I think I've gotten pretty bad with the knocks and the constant
Harassment from this guy, and it's like and she's sitting on a panel with him
And this guy is like and he's also done stuff to her too, and it's like I don't know
It's like she's fine sitting on the panel
She never necessarily laughed at that part of it like but she was laughing at other parts with them
So okay, and so do you know what though? I'm not a big fan of Disney, but
One thing comes to mind, let it go, let it go, just move on though.
I know I will, but you know what? I need to like just let my side, like tell my side of the story
and defend myself because I've been just basically being...
Walked over and it's like I need to be I need to grow a pair and so but I'm gonna I'm not gonna bother her
I'm not gonna go to her chat. I'm not gonna start calling her. I'm not it beyond this. This is this is the last time
I'm not even gonna mention her. It's like, you know, we can go our separate ways. It's bad
Regrettable. I tried to apologize a billion times for a billion things. She calls me
You know yelling she called me yelling at me several times over things that I
You want to change gear and not talk about this anymore?
Well, yeah, we can. Sure. Go ahead. But it's like, you know, I mean, she's having a live.
I'm sure she's going to be talking about me a lot about it, but I'm not going to be going over there.
We've been looking at it. Great. What would you like to talk about apart from this?
Um, I'd be happy to do a reading for you. I'd be happy to
I don't do readings mate. I'm not into that type of
You are on a tarot show. So what the fuck are you doing here then? I mean, it's like really it's like
But the show's about you know, because
A cult if you're not into metaphysics if you're not into tarot readings
What? Of course I am, but anyway, I understand reality as well. Would you like to talk a bit about reality?
Tell me your version of reality
Did oh, right
Did you see what happened in Virginia today in where Virginia? Yeah, what's what's in the news tell me?
Every single American commander was dragged from every command post in the world to come to one building in Virginia today. Did you say that?
I did not. I don't really keep up with the news because I think a lot of it is just fake.
I believe in a lot of it's just PsyOps and framing of...
I mean, I'm only trying to step it up, trying to make a little break, but anyway,
it was quite disturbing what happened in Virginia today.
I'll let you digest that in your own time.
I'm not going to make this conversation about that.
But anyway, I was just trying to break the momentum because, like, I was there.
You should get out. I said it. I mean it's like what the toothpaste is out of the tube, you know
Whatever's been said has been said on her side on my side. I'm gonna move on. I'm gonna respect your wishes
I'm not gonna go to her chat. I'm not gonna bother her. I'm not gonna call her. I'm not gonna
There's gonna be nothing I'm not gonna poke at her. There's not gonna be any more AI song
I'm not gonna see that and throw away all the ones I made about her
Just know it's like, you know, there's two sides of every story. She was the one saying choose a side
Okay, and the people that you know, there's certain people that you know are smart enough like, you know, they didn't I appreciate those people
To her just like neutral, but but there's a lot of people that just like
You know are very
I'm going to know. Can I ask you a question here, Psyche? Yes. A motion of your audience, IP2 and
IRL Circle Juris. I came out of Benny Blanco, okay, off of Benny like that. He was the first
person to ever promote me. That was Benny Blanco. That's the first person I was doing terror
readings in his chat. He's on IPC. Benny Blanco from the Bronx. No, Benny Blanco is an
from PA, but then I'm friends with Saint Kent and I'm friends with like Trident and I've met,
you know, and I like Elisa Jordana who's not in IP2 anymore, but she was and then, you know,
and also Alex Mayers was on IP2. She has to be removed from IP2. I'm great friends with her
and I've met her in person and I knew her for about a month and she treated me very respectfully
and there's a lot of stuff that went on with her and too that I didn't quite
I mean, it's like, I really didn't like and, you know, and it's like, and also she made
an effort to come meet me in person after like a month and it's like, of all the time
knowing Bita and everything, there's been zero effort to, for anything to ever, ever.
And I did want to, you know, I did want to know that I've been talking to Alexander
Okay, well, do you have anything I hope you know what like I hopefully it's all positive, you know, it's like I
When it comes to IP to an IRL what's positive about it?
Well, that's what I'm saying
I'm starting my own thing where it's like gonna be a friendlier community and basically more of a more spiritual people or
At least like
Not like as toxic. Okay, and I want I want a less toxic
I mean that I P2 is basically kind of like it's basically about the audience and it's like about trolley and stuff like that
That was never my vision for this and it's like I did get sidetracked a lot
And I'm very distracted and stuff like that
There is just like a lot of mean spirit of stuff that I don't care about and I always wanted to like you know be a positive force in it
I didn't get dragged down into a lot of negativity
um with it but you know what I have the ability to take a new direction and so I will be and
the show will be focused on the occult it'll be focused on metaphysics it'll be focused on
tarot it'll be focused on recovery from narcissistic abuse it'll be you know protection against toxic
personalities which I do have a lot of experience but technically all you put yourself in a bubble
Well, you know what I need a little bubble of protection if I need to like if I need to whatever however, I want to run my show
That's how I'm gonna run my show. Okay, and so
She was always like do this do this run it like this
Don't take this don't have this person on but have this person on don't keep you guys just telling me what to do
How to run it she has a problem with how I type of my thing
She has a problem with my AI music the problem with this and this and this and this I mean she has just so many problems
There's nothing positive
come out in a long time. And I love this, I love her. Okay, I got a fucking tattoo of this, of her,
of her freaking thing. Okay, stupid me, whatever. But now it stands for be kind gang, the be kind
dance. Are you saying you put a female's name on your body? No, I didn't, I didn't, I put, I, I do
have an Arabic style.
Dang, but I can very easily stand for something else.
Arabic style, do you mean Jewish, did you mean Arabic or Aramaic or Jewish?
Excuse me?
What did you mean?
Oh, did you mean Arabic or Aramaic or Jewish?
I mean Hebrew.
I didn't say it's not any, okay, well, first of all, I mean,
First of all, I do have studied Hebrew, I have studied Kabbalah, okay, whether you call
Judaism a race or a religion or that kind of thing, whatever Christianity grew out of
Judaism, okay, and so did...
Muslim, okay, that grew out of that grew out of Judaism. Okay, they're all Abrahamic religion, okay, so
What the original or was written in right but then they have the Talmud which was an oral tradition, okay?
And so yes, I understand I've studied it a lot. Okay. I I'm not some like I said some
Do me a favor. Please tell me you don't follow the Talmud. Please.
I don't follow it. I've studied the Talmud. I don't think that I think it says really
disgusting things about Jesus. I like Jesus's message. I don't like saying Mary the hairdresser.
I don't like saying Jesus is burning, excrement in hell, and you know, all this kind of other
kind of stuff, right? And I know there's a lot of controversial stuff that has been,
that's why the reason it was an oral tradition. You know, I don't agree with everything. I have
Kabbalah, you know, and it's like there is like a lot of
Light in that I will say and that's he says esoteric Judaism, you know, and I've studied that carefully
But I've also said very
Deism I mean, can you explain esoteric Judaism to me please come on?
Every religion will have an exoteric side which is like what is presented to the masses and it will have an esoteric side which is like
For the people that study into depth, into their secret meanings, there's other meanings.
Okay, so it's like, you know, just like, you know, in Tibetan Buddhism, I'm initiated in Bajrayana, right?
And it's like, and so that is the esoteric Buddhism, or else they, but they also have, you know, the normal Buddhism, right?
But everyone's taught, and then they have secret teachings and things like that, and so which usually require
an initiative by a teacher.
Which I have that shirts. Okay, and so don't you don't need to like, you know, you can test me on things
But I'll say I'm just
Setting me I mean the old testament's very violent just like the Talmud
The jail is God. He's also you know, so destroy all your enemies and throw their
since stuff like that. I mean, it's pretty scary in the Old Testament, right?
And then the New Testament, Jesus comes, and it's like, he's like the love,
he's like the God of love, and it's also various episodes.
That's why I don't follow Abrahamic religions at all.
Right. Well, I'm just saying all I'll say is I've studied them very carefully
I read the entire I read the entire Torah or the Old Testament and I scanned an Aramaic and I did learn Hebrew
Okay, it is like not like I'm perfect at it, but I do know let the letters and things right and
You know
Basically, I've studied so much
of it, that it's like, you know, religion is basically like a boat. You use it to get across the river, right?
But once you're on the other side, you need to carry the boat around with you, you know, you don't.
So I've gotten to the other side, and I don't know, you can say I'm, you know, people can say whatever they want.
I have my own relationship with the divine, and...
Can I just confront you with the religions you've studied, with the passive, let's just
say, can we say, religions of a certain value that's very pagan, okay, well pagan so you're
like, you know, well, I mean this shit, you
Sorry, I've never said that. I mean the card reading things like that. We can the bones
These are things that are sort of like no no's in the Abramics, but you follow those type of
I was, I was in the Church of Satan at 18 years old, okay, so as soon as I could, I was...
Look, you're just 18 years old, fuck me now!
I was, I was, I studied at, that was like, you know, 12 years old, and I had been tarot since I was 8 years old.
And so, yeah, that's my kid.
Yes.
What?
I had!
My first text was the the tarot of the cat people and probably my second deck was called mythic tarot and I
I've been it's my life. It's been my lifetime
passion
Very transient your beliefs very transient in your beliefs, but when it comes to YouTube you won't let people talk sense
I love people saying whatever they want, but other people's relationship to God is none
of my business.
That is between them and God.
And so, give me the same respect.
I have my own relationship with God.
Or shall we see monotheism and polytheism when it comes to that sort of sense?
You know different, you know, but they say like
There's literally billions of gods, you know, it's more guys than there are stars in the Hinduism, okay?
And then or there's like thought like, you know
You know, the monotheism where there's one God, but still there were, if you read into it, there are still other gods, and people worship other gods, and it got connected.
Believe America's becoming very monotheism, and it's called orange monotheism, to be honest.
America? Well, yeah, but America, I'd say, is more like consumerism, I think, is more of the religion of America, right?
I mean there's people of all it is freedom of religion. It's also freedom from religion
Forced to either live under religious law like are the ten commandments?
No, are they laws in america?
But um without getting kicked off it's like
Do you see what happened in virginia today fella explain it against me what happens? I didn't fully catch it every single
A military leader, commander, captain, colonel, admiral, general were summoned to one building
in Quantico, Virginia today.
You know, you know, you know,
you know, you know, you know,
No, I didn't and what do you have something kind of durable on a tank? What is that?
Like what is the point of that right? You didn't finish, but I said it could you imagine a country's
military leadership
being dragged to one building
to be heard by one person to do it.
I don't understand the point of it.
I really don't follow just like regular news
because I think it's all bunch of bullshit, most news.
But anyway, it's not bullshit what happened today, mate.
It's very disturbing.
So everyone told us about some building.
Everyone was summoned to one building.
What's the deal?
Tell me what's the importance in your mind.
I want to hear.
Well, no, it's very disturbing, especially what
Pete Edsex had to say and Donald Trump.
Okay, well, you know, this is like getting into politics, which is not really the focus on
it's not politics. It's about what's was said today. It's got fuck all I do with politics.
It's about optics. Optics. Okay. Optics. So have vision or what? Like, um, what?
Explain, explain. I don't get your point. What's your point, sir?
Right. My point is, if you don't believe what they say, now you're a person of interest.
And you're going to have the military point. Is it you in your over? Oh
Now you've like gotten me now. I'm not in the military scope. Well, I know plenty of military people
There's plenty of military people in the chat. Oh, I lost connection to something. Hold on. Do you hear me?
So do you still hear me? I lost connections in my brain. Okay. What's that on say? It says the browser is blocked
Your screen. Okay, and I don't know. Yeah. Um, well, that's why I don't get into politics because
Then it's like what I don't want to be some kind of target for some political belief, right?
And it's like and so if you're trying to get me into a corner and say I believe this or this and you're not going
Focus of the show and if you continue on the path when I say I don't know anything about it explain your point of view
Listen listen
My point is
I'm on the humans
You don't know what's happened today, but it's very substantial
Okay, well, maybe I was gonna do it. I've had other stuff going on right now
I'm in my personal life. Okay. And so to be focused on the news
So I haven't seen the exact news story you're talking about. I've you know, maybe I'm just in tunnel vision in the panel versus whatever
People can you know at this point
Everything that horrible that's been said has been said if you're gonna be you know be here like not just you
But it's like if people don't want to be here can be here. You don't like me
If you don't want to focus on tarot, I really don't have a
Something to offer because it's like I'm a tarot card reader and I can discuss
Right again, you won't read my tarot's but there
I did
So I'm not going to because I respect whatever people would like I'm not gonna force it on people
But if you're here, you tell me what the world
Tarot will be please with what the world what it would you say asking what it means or what is it?
Well, what do you mean what it will be? No, can you tell a tarot for human society, please?
Can I pull a tarot for human society? Yes, okay?
For this it's for for human humanity in general like right
I'd be happy just one card or what?
You do you do what you've got to do you are the psych after all
Yeah, I'll do three cards as in general what's going on with humanity as a whole. Okay, that's interesting question. Okay
We can have a look into the energy of humanity. Can we look into humanity as a whole?
What's what is the general energy with humanity right now? Okay.
Okay. Oh, we have the 10 of cups. Okay.
10 of Cubs, okay, is a very good card because this is like the ultimate happiness and so there is like a happily ever-after
Here somewhere. Okay, there's 10 of Cubs is
Celebrating it's with the it's with your family. It's just all good thing 10 of Cubs is just an abundance of good emotion
Okay, so there's I see there are there is a lot of positive, okay?
Okay, but that this is also there's three cards that could be
in the past, but we also have the emperor, okay?
Emperor, this is the one with the authority,
the one that's in charge.
This is like, this is perfect for the present moment
because, oh, oh, oh, did I just?
Yeah, I'm sorry. Yeah, the emperor right the ultimate authority rests with him
And this is almost like I feel like a world leader rather than just like a certain leader
I think and this is also the authority, right? This is like or who's in charge, okay? The emperor, okay?
So the ruler of all right, okay?
What's in the future? Okay, ten of cubs. We've had a happy path right now
It's in the control of the rulers, right? Well, what's what's what's the what is the future for us?
Okay, what is the future of humanity, right? We're in our authority. We're in our authority. We have a happy paths
Or some kind of happy maybe the happiness happiest part is gone, okay, we have the hermit in reverse, okay?
This is the time of like getting out of our selfishness and coming together as a community
this is the time out of rather than being on solitary journeys into coming together and
having multiple, multiple groups.
It's not about solitude anymore.
It's about the collective, I would say.
I would say that's what this represents right there.
Could you tell me how much collective community
survives around the world today?
Survive? What do you mean?
Like what collective survives?
Because you know what?
Whether there's a person or there's eight million people.
May come on are you are you listening to me at all go ahead to get your point please
well there's no community there's no collective there's only one collective going on and that's
superiority of a collective who wants to control humanity
Well, I think we can also come together as a people there's a collective of human beings, right?
And it's like that's ultimately what we're about with nobody is a island
We are all connected to each other and so despite like, you know, there is like a lot of I think, you know
Selfishness, but I think that's gonna change. I think it's we're going to the age of Aquarius, right and Aquarius is the air sign
I am an Aquarian and I'm informing you, I'm informing you, the world's getting fucked up deliberately by you.
The world is an illusion, my friend. The world is an illusion. We are all temporary beings on this planet, okay?
But what is real is the spirit and the spirit is one, okay?
Or all, you know, the spirit and this is just an illusion that we are working through things through all these bodies and
this duality, which is multiple, right? It's like, but there's a secret
Unity with everything, okay, and it's like there's not any human being or even
Animal being or or piece of life. It's all life. It's life and even death is
Life, okay life and death
The lights the light and the life is being sucked out of every country
I mean, I know you don't pay attention to global events, but the world is getting a life.
I'm the wife
Because the world is a temporary thing the world will be just the world will be destroyed and new worlds will be created
You know it goes on and on forever just as a cycle of you know
Created or destroyed it can only be transformed me
You're talking about one of physics right if it cannot be created this right it can only change form the energy the light
Well, it's always there. The same water that is on this planet is the same water that was on the planet a billion years
The human language when it's controlled control too many cunts
That the world cannot be happy of the human factor at all
Well, you know what if whether we destroy ourselves or we figure out a way out of it
It's still this temporary thing because we will all pass away. There's not gonna be a way that we're all just gonna like
You know live forever in this one body, right? We're gonna constantly die and the energy will transform
Whether it transforms into like a tree or it transforms into like a cloud or whether whatever it transforms into it
Constantly is in a process of transformation. Okay? Everything the transformation is jackboots and nutty ism
quite front but we already had that and we can have it again and the history repeats itself and
it's like you can look back there's always been these violent times and it's like there's just
cycles and cycles and cycles it keeps going around and around and around and we're going to go back
to the caveman again and we're going to go all the way to the fucking you know the robots running
everything and then back to the big that that's going to destroy itself and then we're going to be
whatever you've been smoked tonight because it looks fucking
champion. I just spoken with you. Yeah, but what what type of
weed are you smoking there, fella? It's a Tiva. That's a
Tiva. What time of day is it where you're? It is 6 30 PM. I
suggest you switch the indica right now.
Well, that's when I want to go to sleep. That's going to be a little bit when it's a nighttime, you know
Then I will be but I'm just trying to listen. I just had a nap. I just had a nap all day
I've had a long day too. I've it's been very emotional. It's been an emotional time. I've been having my sleep schedule
Destroyed by people knocking on the door looking for scrap metal at all times of the day. Not their fault
Not their fault. They're nice people. There's all kinds of people that I've met
Oh, they all have
That's why I came up here to change gear to take your mind off it fella. Well, thank you
I appreciate that and I hope that I've been opened it a discussion. I'm not trying to like, you know really debate
I'm just trying to
come to
Peace. I'm trying to peace and understand you as well.
I believe Ming-Chan has a big difference.
Sativa and Nidhika has a big difference.
There's hybrid.
Psych. I did come here for you to change gear
because it was like the old mode of ghosts.
Do the same thing every day.
And you expect the same thing you remain and you keep repeating yourself. You keep repeating yourself and
What happened in Virginia today if you don't realize what happened in Virginia today
OK, I'm going to talk about things like that on Google.
So sorry about that.
OK, well.
You know, it's always a pleasure talking to you Vanguard and it's like, you know, you're an intelligent person, but you have to respect an intelligent person too. Don't just count my intelligence.
I didn't disrespect your intelligence. I said I came up to make you change gear and take you off your fucking psychological loop about beta and all the bullshit. That's all. I came up to be nice.
Thank you. Thank you. But, you know, that thought just necessarily gonna, I mean...
I'm done with it. I mean, like I said, like I said, everything I'm going to say about it, it's like, I'm going to continue on with my life.
I'm going to be switching gears a little bit with my show. I'm going to be more focused on what I came here to do, but always maybe going to be
Some kind of like, you know, I am I do have a marketing background to and so, you know, I do like to help people
I want to help people do channels and be successful in channels and all kinds of things
I want to help people with marketing and I want to continue to
Come up with all kinds of
Can I just answer somebody in chat?
Which theory thoughts on the tartaria concept? That's very interesting
Hey, wait, what is it called?
The what?
The Tartania concept.
Tartania concept?
Let me see, hold on.
I can't.
Tartania.
Tartaria.
Okay.
Well, Tartaria, I think, is just basically Russia, you know.
Yeah.
It's just basically Russia.
It's like a fake kind of thing where they had like, you know, unicorn as the fucking,
you know, mascot and stuff.
It's just like, you know, it's just kind of like, you know.
I'll let you talk about the chat about the dartoria concept blues you go ahead
I'll just tell you it's bullshit
It's Russia. Okay. It's just Russia
Okay
Hello
I think I've lost him. Vanguard what happened? Oh, no, hold on what happened?
See
Hello
Are you still there psych
What
I've been missing in my sleep